https://stevensoncompany.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy | TraQline
Chat with us,
powered by LiveChat
Forgot Password
Search for:
Commitment To Your Privacy
Privacy Policy: This site is owned and operated by The Stevenson Company. Your privacy on the internet is of the utmost importance to us. At The Stevenson Company, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel that you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.
Information The Stevenson Company Gathers And Tracks
Under no circumstances does The Stevenson Company divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.
Users may view webpages without providing any Personal Information about yourself. When you request information or register for the TraQline, we request that you provide Personal Information about yourself, and we collect Navigational Information.
Information The Stevenson Company gathers through aggregated tracking information is derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and to help us better understand the demographics of our audience.
Privacy settings are set at a high level, and measures are taken by The Stevenson Company to make sure that the processing, throughout the whole processing lifecycle, complies with the regulation. Any personal data collected is never shared and is not processed unless necessary for each specific purpose.
Information we collect about our users includes information you provide such as: Name, Company, Phone number, Email, Job title, etc.
Information we collect about your use of our website includes: IP address (if available), and Pages visited.
Log Files
When you use TraQline or provide information via a web form, we automatically collect information about your computer hardware and software. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, internet service provider (ISP), the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, access times and referring website addresses. It may also include information pertaining to the reports you viewed, emails requested, and variables used on our subscription website. This information is used by to provide general statistics regarding use of the TraQline Website and to provide more targeted information for our users.
Use of Information
The Stevenson Company uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our site, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. According to the preferences you set, or as the need arises to inform our users of information pertaining to their account, we may contact you from time to time regarding your TraQline subscription or the TraQline website.
We use tracking information to determine which areas of our site users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We track how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search functions as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don’t track which terms a particular user enters.
Users of our site may update their preferences at any time, including the right to “opt-out” of any non-essential email (except for those deemed critical to the functioning of the site, or those communications required by law). Until users opt-out of communications from The Stevenson Company, we may contact you according to the preferences users have set.
Legal Basis for Collection information
Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where we have your consent to do so, where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you.
If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information). Similarly, if we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.
Sharing Of The Information
The Stevenson company uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help us better understand our audience’s demographics. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.
Data breach reporting
Data breaches must be reported within 72 hours of discovering the breach.
If the breach poses or may pose a risk to customers (I.e. passwords being leaked), they must be notified directly.
Data retention for European clients
Should one of our European clients terminate our agreement, we will delete any no-longer-necessary data within a reasonable period of time.
Right to request a copy of the data
Any European user may request a copy of any personal information we have on them as well as the purpose of processing the data, with whom the data is shared (see section above – “Sharing of The Information”, and how the data was acquired.
Right of Erasure
You may request your information to be erased at any time for any reason.
To Unsubscribe From Our Communications
You may unsubscribe from our communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our e-mails, updating your communication preferences, or by sending us email us at info@stevensoncompany.com or postal mail to The Stevenson Company, 10002 Shelbyville Road, Suite 201, Louisville, KY 40223, Attention: Privacy.
TraQline™
FAQ
Insights
TraQline US™
TraQline Canada™
Deliverables
Privacy Policy
Research Services
Social
Copyright 2020. TraQline.
Our site uses cookies to determine which areas of our site users visit most frequently. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process. By clicking "I accept" on this banner or using our site, you consent to the use of cookies unless you have disabled them.I acceptPrivacy policy
